Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 11.02.17 01:39:31
前情提要
[Narrator] Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
你到底怎么回事？
What is going on with you?
医院同意了你可以
We grant you four months to retake the medical board exam.
四个月后补考临床医理
Karev,接着解剖刀. Alex! 接啊!
- Karev, take the scalpel. - Alex, come on.
你的选择? 非常简单，她还是我.
Your choice. It's simple. Her or me.
Addison是我的家人. 然后有一天,
Addison is my family. I'm supposed to sign a piece of paper and end my family?
我需要签一张纸 来断绝和家人的关系?
你要和那个人约会? 那是我老公.
- Your date? - My husband.
你已经结婚了? 今天整整10年.
- You're married? - Ten years today.
Burke想和我确立关系
Burke wants a relationship.
Okay,我们是一对了.
OK. We're a couple.
那么选我. 要我.
So pick me. Choose me. Love me.
爱我. 我今晚会在Joe的酒吧.
I'll be at Joe's tonight. If you decide to sign the papers, meet me there.
如果你决定签那张纸了 过来找我.
告诉我，该怎么办.
Tell me what to do.
我竟然说了 "选我."
I actually said "Pick me." Right? I did? "Pick me"?
对吗? 我说了? "选我"?
-我觉得这挺浪漫的. -一点也不浪漫,joe.
- I think it's romantic. - It's not romantic, it's horrifying.
那是恐怖.
Horror movie horrifying. Carrie at the prom with the pig's blood horrifying.
恐怖片的恐怖情节. （恐怖片《Carrie》）
就像Carrie在一场舞会上 满身猪血的恐怖.
Okay,好吧, 的确恐怖.
OK, fine, it's horrifying.
但是作为报复， Carrie带走了所有高年级生.
But Carrie took out an entire senior class as revenge.
我必须承认 我就喜欢那种姑娘.
Gotta say, I like that in a girl.
我说了 "选我."
I said "Pick me."
当你告诉某人我晚一些时候 会在酒吧等你,
When you say "I'll meet you later"
到底意味着你会等多久?
how long does that mean you should wait?
- Do you think he's really not coming? - It is getting a little hard to watch.
你认为他真的不会来吗?
即使在这里看着都有点难
It was hard to watch an hour ago. Now it's pathetic.
一个钟头前就够难了 现在不过是可悲而已.
谁可悲?
Who's pathetic?
什么?
- What? - You, who pretend to be my friends,
你们应该算是我的朋友吧
竟然说我可悲? 在我背后
are calling me pathetic behind my back in front of my face.
在我面前.
Why don't you just dump the pig's blood on me now and get it over with?
为什么你们不把猪血倒我身上
你们不就完成任务了吗?
[Beeping]
看来他真不会来了.
He's really not coming.
[Beeping]
Joe,把电视声音调大些.
[Man] Joe, turn up the TV.
(女主播) 一场大规模的火车失事
[TV] A massive train wreck occurred just outside Seattle minutes ago.
几分钟前发生在西雅图近郊
911? 我们刚刚工作了30个钟头啊.
- 911. - We just worked a 30-hour shift.
我都没有干净的内裤穿了
- I don't have any clean underwear. - [They sigh]
vancouver驶来的火车
The Vancouver-bound train was carrying 300 passengers.
满载300名乘客
- Looks ugly. - Paramedics are helping victims.
看起来真糟糕. 救护人员正在现场帮助救治伤者
你要走了? 不不不,你不能走.
You're leaving? No, you can't leave.
对不起.我要去帮助其他人的"火车失事"了.
Sorry, gotta go tend to someone else's train wreck.
你至少要留下来再喝杯咖啡
You gotta at least stay for a cup of coffee.
你现在绝对不适合给别人开刀.
You're in no shape to cut people open. I want to hear the ending.
另外,我不想错过大结局.
Meredith?
Maybe it's for the best. Maybe I don't want to know.
也许现在就是最好的结局了. 也许我根本不想知道结局如何
That's the stupidest thing I've ever heard.
这是我从来没听过的最愚蠢的说法.
(meredith) 大致来说,
- [Meredith] In general... - Bye, Joe.
人可以被划分为2种类型...
...people can be categorized in one of two ways.
[Man] He was in the front of the train.
一种是喜欢突发事件的
Those who love surprises, and those who don't.
以及另外一种不喜欢的.
我...
I don't.
不喜欢.
(女主播) 一个损坏的发动机部件
在火车离开车站的两小时前得到确认
但却致使火车准时出发.
Dude, you're late.
伙计,
[TV] Once again, a massive train wreck occurred outside of Seattle minutes ago.
你迟到了.
我从没遇到过一个外科医生是喜欢突发事件的
[Meredith] I've never met a surgeon that enjoys a surprise,
因为做为医生, 我们更喜欢了解全局.
because, as surgeons, we like to be in the know.
我们必须要了解全局.
We have to be in the know.
因为有时候, 当我们无法了解全局时,
Because when we aren't, people die and lawsuits happen.
患者死亡 然后官司就跟着来了.
Am I rambling? I think I'm rambling.
我散漫吗? 我觉得我挺散漫的.
[Cristina] I think I saw a pneumothorax. I hope I get a pneumothorax.
- Hey. - Thought you weren't talking to me.
我好像看到了一个气胸患者. 真希望能分到一个气胸的.
Thought you needed a friend, so I'm rising above.
我以为你再也不理我了
-我以为你只是把我当朋友 所以我也就只把你当朋友而已. -那么为什么你这样认为呢?
- Why would you think that? - Because you freaked out.
因为你在电梯里吓傻了?
- I did not. - Missed out on open-heart surgery.
-我才没吓傻呢. -失去了一个表演心脏手术的机会?
O'malley只不过用手指堵住了洞而已
- O'Malley plugged the hole. - I thought you needed to talk.
-我以为你会找什么人聊聊 -我没有想过.
- Well, I don't. - To someone who cares about you.
-找个真正关心你的人聊聊 -谢谢你的关心,但是我不需要
Wow. 你们看什么呢?
- What are you looking at? - Is that a dress?
什么也没看. Oh,没什么.
Nothing. What?
Hey,你, 去把的鞋拿来.
Go get me my damn shoes.
这里.
Let's move, people.
大家动起来.
Hello.
Hello. I seem to be a little bit drunk. I was off duty.
我看起来有点醉了
今天我不值班.
So was I. Anybody else half in the bottle?
我也不值班. 还有人喝了半瓶以上酒的吗?
Uh,no. No.
- No. - [Bailey] All right then.
那么好吧.
Stay out of the way. I'll deal with you later.
Grey,站旁边去吧. 我过会儿再处理你.
The rest, stick with me and wait for assignments.
其他人跟着我来 等我给你们分配工作.
我知道当你们看到鲜血和脏器 的时候激动的浑身颤抖,
I know you get all a-quiver at the sight of blood,
但是这个将持续整夜 而你们已经很累了.
but it'll be a long night and you're tired. I want no mistakes. Come on.
我不希望你们犯任何错误. 快点啊!
I'm done. Done.
[Patient groaning]
[Monitors beep]
-我一点一点也不累了. -我也不,一点也不累.
- I'm so not tired anymore. - Me neither.
我这里有一个三度烧伤患者
I've got a third-trimester burn victim here. I'll need some help.
Bailey医生,我需要帮忙
- Izzie, go. - Yes. Have a nice nap.
Uh,izzie,去吧.
Yes! 睡个好觉!
有宫缩了吗? 没有.
- Have you had any contractions? - No.
Hey. Joe told me to tell you that McSteamy came looking for you.
-joe让我告诉你,"美闷先生"过去找你来着 -你是说"美梦先生"
You mean McDreamy? Joe said McDreamy came looking for me?
Joe说"美梦先生"去找我了?
No, I'm pretty sure it was McSteamy. Yeah. Yeah.
No,我很确定是"美闷先生".
Yeah.
Shepherd医生,能看看这个吗?
Dr. Shepherd, could you take a look at this?
这是意味着他选她了吗?
Does that mean he picked her?
如果是的话,我刚刚输了50块钱
If it does, I just lost 50 bucks.
腿来了!
Got the leg!
-我要那条腿! -他在现场就大量失血.
- I want that leg. - He lost a lot of blood at the scene.
-伤口已经止血了, 两个注射针头已经插入动脉了. -给什么止痛的了吗?
Pressure dressings applied, two large-bore IVs started.
- Anything for pain? - Morphine. Five migs given so far.
基本用量的吗啡,现在为止给了5毫克了
Bailey医生, 你那有谁?
Dr. Bailey, who you got?
Oh! Oh!
- Cristina, go. - Yes!
Cristina,去.
-取消其他一切伤患,预约一个手术室 -Yes,sir.
Rule out other injuries and book an OR.
-Webber医生. -我们有个火车失事,derek.
- Dr. Webber? - We have a train wreck, Derek.
我们需要全部人手 所以现在就帮我做清理手术
We need all hands on deck. Clear me for surgery or you're fired.
-否则你就下岗. -今天头疼了吗?
- Any headaches today? - No.
-没有. -眩晕?恶心?视力模糊?
- Dizziness? Nausea? Blurred vision? - No, no and no. Out of my way.
-没有没有就没有. 现在别档着我的路. -好吧,那我跟你一起去.
Fine. But I'm coming with you. Or I'm fired. Up to you.
或者我下岗,你决定.
[Woman on PA] If you're a resident, page the operator.
-他是对你点头了吗? -是
- Was that a nod? - Yes.
-我们知道那是什么意思吗? -不知道
- Do we know what it meant? - No.
我是隐形人吗?
Am I invisible?
Okay, 其实我要说的重点是,
[Meredith] OK, so my point actually, and I do have one,
我的确是有重点的
has nothing to do with surprises or death or lawsuits or even surgeons.
对待突发事件,我们无计可施
或者死亡或者吃官司 即使是医生也无法避免.
我想说的是... 某人说过
My point is this; whoever said, "What you don't know can't hurt you"
"未知的事物是无法伤害你的"
真是个宇宙超级无敌大白痴
was a complete and total moron.
因为就大多数我认识的人来说,
Because for most people I know,
一无所知是世界上第一糟糕的事情了
not knowing is the worst feeling in the world.
Okay,算了.
OK, fine, maybe it's the second worst.
也许是第二糟糕的
Grey's Anatomy  206 Into You Like A Train
他的血压保持在90上下.
His BP's steady at ninety over palp.
她曾出现两次低血压,均低于70
She's had two hypotensive episodes to the low seventies.
-你在现场的时候找不到一个锯吗? -找不到
- Couldn't get a saw in? - Not without moving them.
那肯定是个坏主意.
- Which would've been a bad idea. - [Burke] Did you bolus her with fluids?
你把那药丸给她吃了吗?
[Paramedic] We're pushing it open...
这是你见过的最疯狂的事情吗?
Is this the craziest thing you've seen?
Um,yeah.
Uh... Yeah.
Yeah. 我也是.
Yeah. Me too.
那么好吧,你们从这里接手吧.
OK, then. You guys got it from here.
Hey,uh,你当时在现场吗?
Hey, uh... You were at the scene?
Yeah. Won't be too bad for you. Lot of carnage. Not a lot of survivors.
Yeah.对你来说不会太糟糕
血流遍野,没有几个幸存者
他俩肯定没办法做c.t了.
They're never gonna fit into CT. We're gonna be flying blind.
我们要靠运气了.
Get X-rays and labs, then page me.
做x-rays和所有测试 做好了就传呼我
请问.
Excuse me?
Hi,我是Burke医生.
Hi, I'm Dr. Burke.
你不应该转头.
You shouldn't turn your head. You want to try to move as little as possible.
你现在试着移动,尽可能的小幅度.
Oh,okay.
Oh. OK.
你会把这根竿子尽快拔出来吗
So are you gonna pull this pole out of us anytime soon?
这个碰起来不是很舒服.
Touch uncomfortable.
对不起,我们现在无法移动它.
Sorry, we can't until we get a better look at what's going on internally.
除非掌握了里面的情况.
I assure you we will work as quickly as possible.
但是我向你们保证,我们会尽快解决
那么,既然这样的话, 谁有薄荷口香糖?
Well, in that case, does anybody have a breath mint?
给我的,不是给你.
For me, not for you.
带他们去吧.
- Keep them going. - O'Malley? Get them to X-ray.
Uh,o'malley,带他们去做x-ray.
谢谢.
- Thanks. - Move them extremely carefully.
移动的时候千万小心
这个在"电梯急救"之前,绝对没希望发生.
This never would've happened before the elevator.
去吧,george.
You go, George.
Alex,去急诊室帮忙缝合吧.
Alex, cover the ER.
You can do sutures while you get over your newfound fear of scalpels.
那样可以帮助你平复对手术刀的恐惧.
那意味着,即使对你而言
That was mean, even for you.
你可是真醉了 去拿袋葡萄糖
You are drunk.
Go get yourself a banana bag IV, put it in your arm and then find me.
注射在你自己胳膊上,然后过来找我.
Do not speak to any more patients, do not practice any medicine.
不许和任何病人说话.
不许帮助救治
Well, should I just go home?
那我干脆回家算了?
Unless you drank the whole bottle, you'll be sober in a few hours.
除非你喝了整整一瓶龙舌兰
你过一会就会镇静下来了.
And the IV fluids will head off your hangover.
静脉注射能阻止你宿醉.
然后你就能帮助救治那些危急的伤者了
Then you can assist with the many mangled victims here.
你看到了你面前这一片一片的病人.
Besides, if I'm not going home, nobody's going home.
另外还有,如果我没回家的话, 谁也不许回家
结婚十周年.
Ten years of marriage. I didn't even get to finish my damn lobster.
我甚至还没吃完那该死的龙虾呢.
Well,um,你需要我给你的什么人打电话吗
Well, is there anyone you'd like me to call?
No,他们已经在救护车上给我老婆打电话了.
They called my wife from the ambulance.
还有我未婚夫.他们正一起 从vancouver飞过来呢.
And my fiancé. They're flying down from Vancouver together.
一般来说amanda 肯定会有点生气
Normally, Amanda would be upset to find me pressed up against another woman.
当她看到我和另外一个女人挤在一起的话
但是现在这种情况,我想我没事的.
But in this case, I think I'll get a pass.
你们俩不是一起旅行的吗?
- You two weren't traveling together? - No. We just met.
No,我们刚刚认识.
- [Man] Bit of an awkward introduction. - You have very nice pores.
这个出场介绍有点难看
你毛孔非常细致.
[Laughs, groans] Hurts to laugh.
Oh,笑起来可真疼.
Hey. Hey.
- Hey. - Hey.
Whoa.
- Whoa. You can go ahead and just... - Oh, thanks.
你可以先来. Oh,thanks.
- [Clears throat] - Oh, wow.
Oh,wow.
- Do you think I could... - Yeah, go ahead.
你觉得,uh, 我可以... yeah,过去吧.
Stevens医生, 你有什么需要的吗?
Dr. Stevens, did you need something?
没有.
No.
Ow.
- Ow! - I'm sorry. Am I doing this too...
Oh,对不起. 我做的这个太..
ow! Ow!
- Ow! Was that a... Did I have... - A contraction.
那是...
我是...
It was definitely a contraction. We need to book an OR.
一次宫缩. 绝对是一次宫缩.
我们需要去找个手术室
You are in no shape to push, and the baby is still in some distress,
听着,虽然你并没有有意的向外推
但是婴儿还是处在一个危险的状态.
so we're gonna have to proceed with a C-section.
我们还是要做剖腹产手术
Okay.
OK. OK.
Okay,可以先把我律师叫来吗?
But can we call a lawyer first?
我还没立遗嘱呢
I don't have a will. And there's no father.
而且孩子没有父亲.
万一我发生什么意外的话
And in case something happens to me...
根本不需要惊慌, brooke,我们有大把时间呢,okay?
There's no cause for panic, Brooke. We have some time, OK?
Okay.
OK.
Hello.
- [cell phone rings] - [Woman] Hello.
Oh,不,不 我们挺好的,亲爱的
Oh, no, no, no, we're fine, honey.
Yeah,一些农民想要超火车
Some redneck tried to outrun the train.
亲爱的,火车撞上他的屁股了 然后滚了几圈.
The train slammed into his ass and then it rolled...
这疼吗? Unh-unh.
- That hurt? - Uh-uh.
Oh,不不不不 那哥们都傻B了.
Oh, no, no, that dude is toast.
亲爱的,他和其他200多人呢.
Him and about 200 other people.
mary的整个脸都撞变形了
- And Mary got her face all cut up. - Does it hurt anywhere else?
-这疼吗?其他地方呢? -这里
Here.
他们急刹车的时候
A whole bunch of luggage, when they hit the brakes, it just came flying at us.
一整排的行李都冲我们飞过来了.
嗯,好了, 我们要带你去拍个x-ray,
We'll do an X-ray, see if anything's broken, or if there's internal injuries.
看哪里有破损,或者有什么内伤
Okay.
OK.
Yeah,等等,等会
Yeah. Wait. Hold on. I'm gonna have to call you back.
我一会再打给你
- Hey. Excuse me. Where you going? - I'm taking your friend for an X-ray.
Hey,hey,hey, 对不起,请问
-Um,你们去哪里啊? -我带你朋友去拍x-ray.
[Laughs] No offense, little boy, but you look like my oldest son,
没有恶意,小男孩
你看起来跟我大儿子一样大(这还没恶意?)
- and he's nothing but trouble. - Yvonne, shut up.
他除了到处惹麻烦之外,还基本是个好孩子
-Yvonne,闭嘴吧. -我说了"没恶意",我刚刚说了
I said "no offense." I'm just saying, sure you're a doctor?
你确定你是个医生吗
[Cell phone rings]
Yeah? Oh,yeah,yeah, 我们没事
Yeah? Yeah, we're fine.
Yeah,没错,一些农民开着汽车超火车
Yeah, this redneck tried to outrun the train...
Ow.
[woman] Ow! Ow. Ow.
- What are you doing? - Trying to insert my banana bag.
你干吗呢?
正在试图帮自己静脉注射
Which sounds vaguely dirty, but it isn't.
听起来有点暧昧不清嗯?但其实一点都不.
我来吧.
I can do it.
那个..addison那婆娘怎么样?
So, how's it going with Addison?
坏心情?还是好心情
Bad mood? Good mood? "Yay, my husband picked me" mood?
还是"Yay,我老公选我啦"的心情?
Uh,我觉得更像是
I think it's more of an "I hate the smell of charred flesh" mood.
"我讨厌那菜鸟的味道"的心情
在你对我下判断之前,
Before you judge me, I know there was a train accident.
我了解刚刚一起火车事故
People are very badly hurt.
人们都伤的很重
And that I'm a vapid narcissist when you mix me with alcohol.
而我又如此顾影自怜的自我安慰
当你们灌我喝酒的时候
In case you were wondering, I know that.
只是防止万一你想知道这些 我知道你想.
那么,看看到底哪个值得,
Well, for what it's worth, I take issue with her salmon-colored scrubs.
我觉得她丫是在那儿装没事
I mean, what self-respecting surgeon wears salmon-colored scrubs?
我是说,丫可真是个自尊自爱的好医生
穿一身保护色伪装自己?
- This is what I'm saying. - Yeah.
这就是我要说的 Yeah.
[Richard] Thank you.
谢谢.
[Richard] Yang, how's that wound looking?
Yang,那个伤口看起来怎样?
[Cristina] Pretty clean. Some dirt and gravel.
还挺干净的.大部分只是泥土和沙砾
这家伙还挺幸运的.这可是致命伤害啊
He was lucky. It's a guillotine injury.
如果我们做的没错的话... 他还能继续使用一对完整的大腿.
We do this right, he'll have full use of his leg.
- [Richard] More irrigation. - [pager beeps]
Shepherd医生?
Dr. Shepherd?
它得等着.
[Derek] lt'll wait.
我没事,derek. 只是需要调整一下灯光.
I'm fine, Derek. Just adjusting to the light.
我只是想说,不用觉得可耻
There's no shame in taking more time off.
不过是需要多一点时间休息罢了.
It doesn't make you old or tired or rusty, it...
并不意味着你老了, 或者疲劳了,抑或反映迟钝了.
[pager beeps]
Yeah,okay, 说这些有点过火了.
OK, that came out wrong.
你是唯一的神经科主治医生
You're the only attending neurosurgeon, you're needed elsewhere. I'm fine here.
很明显,其他地方更需要你 我在这里没问题.
[Nurse] Dr. Shepherd?
如果需要我的话,呼我
[Derek] OK. Page me if you need me.
当你清理干净那伤口的时候
[Richard] When you're finished cleaning that wound, you can help me, Dr. Yang.
你可以过来帮我,yang医生
那伤口干净了吗yang?
Is the wound clean, Yang?
Yes,sir. 那个...但是...
- Yes, sir, I... But... - But what?
但是什么?
If your plan is to be a watchdog for Dr. Shepherd
如果你是想给Shepherd医生做只看门狗
或者你认为你的职责是做我的保姆的话
or if you think your job here is to baby-sit me, then you can think again.
那你就继续想下去吧
I've been a surgeon longer than you've been breathing.
我当医生的日子比你吃饭的日子都长
如果我没做好准备就站在这手术室里的话
If I were not ready to be in this OR, I would say so. Is that understood?
-我会直接说出来,够清楚吗? -是的,先生
- Yes, sir. - Now do we have a problem, Yang?
-那我们现在还有问题吗 yang? -Uh,yes.
Yes. No, sir.
没有,先生,我诚惶诚恐的跟您学习.
I'm thrilled to learn. And I'm grateful to be here.
非常感激可以做您的助手,只不过...
It's just that...
那个...
Um...
um...
Sorry. His legs...
对不起,他的两条腿...
两条腿怎么了?
[Richard] What about them?
两条腿都是左腿
[Cristina] They're both left.
去把这爷们的腿找回来,yang.
- Find the man's leg, Yang. Find it now. - Yes, sir.
-现在就去找. -是的先生.
Is it going straight through her spine?
这个是将直接穿过她的脊骨吗?
是啊.T8脊神经完全破碎了.
It is. T8's completely crushed.
Hey.
怎么了?
What happened?
Uh,龙舌兰.
Uh, tequila.
我一直看着她呢.
I'm keeping an eye on her.
看这个.
[Derek] Look at this. These people are still alive?
-这俩人还活着呢吗? -他们还闲聊的挺开心呢.
They're still making small talk.
竿子把那伤口全部填塞了
Pole's tamponading the wounds as far as we can see.
挡的我们什么都看不到了
It's hitting the aorta.
这竿子正撞向大动脉呢.
And look at him. It's right in line with his inferior vena cava.
看那男人那边,正好在他右边 次级腔静脉的那条线上.
有什么办法能不分开他们而同时手术吗?
Is there any way to operate without separating them?
No.
- No. - But if we move the pole then...
-如果我们移动那竿子... -他俩都会大量出血
They'll both bleed out.
如果我们不移动那竿子会如何?
What if we don't move the pole?
如果我们只把其中一个病人 从竿子上弄下来
What if we move one of the patients off the pole to get the saw in there?
用锯在那儿切开会如何?
然后我们就可以握着竿子 而稳定住另外一个了.
Then we can hold the pole steady in the other one.
非常非常慢的移动
Move it very slowly, and repair the damage as we go.
然后再救治那伤口.
Who? Which would you move?
谁? 你打算移动哪个?
照情况来看,那女人大动脉损伤严重,
With her aortic injuries,
她能生存下来的机会微乎其微
her chances of survival are extremely slim no matter what we do.
无论我们怎么做,都于事无补.
But if we move her, we have a real shot at saving him.
但是如果我们把她先弄下来
我们能及时把那男人救回来.
Well, I could argue since her injuries are more extensive, we should move him.
既然这样,我有不同意见 正因为她的伤害比较宽大.
我们应该把那男人先弄下来
Give her the best shot we can.
我们可以全力以赴救治她.
如此说来,无论移动哪个,都是有机会救治的?
So basically whoever you move doesn't stand a chance?
那么你如何选择呢?
So how do you choose? How do you decide who gets to live?
你如何决定谁应该活下来? (共器私用,完全是针对Derek)
我们需要尽快决定 如果想要
We have to decide soon if we want to save one of them.
救治其中一个的话
- I'd like to examine them first. - I'll wait for your page.
-我想在决定之前对他们做个检查 -那我就等你呼我了.
-Grey医生... -Grey医生需要做一个血液酒精浓度测试
Thank you. Dr. Grey?
Dr. Grey needs to get a blood alcohol test before practicing medicine tonight.
在今晚做任何医学实践之前
What? No, I'm totally fine, look. Totally fine.
什么?不用吧.我完全没事了,看着
完全没事
好吧,okay.
Right. OK.
我真的没事
- I'm fine. - Regretting that last shot about now?
现在为上一个射手后悔了吧你?
你在这里做什么呢?
What are you doing in here?
Uh,那个你带来的切断手术患者的腿...
The leg you brought with the amputee...
我没带什么切断手术患者来
- I didn't bring in an amputee. - OK, well, one of you did and it's...
Okay,好,um, 其中一个你...
因为所有的救护人员都和你长的一样 对吗,医生?
'Cause all paramedics look alike to you?
Okay,此时此刻,我实在没时间 和你辩论什么自负自大之类的话题.
OK. Really. I cannot straddle another giant ego right now.
我已经在做那手术了
I'm already doing the splits. I need a right leg, right now,
所以我现在就需要那只右腿
or the Chief of Surgery will take away my pretty blue scrubs.
否则主治医生就会脱掉我 美丽可爱的蓝色医生袍.
当那火车出轨的时候正好撞到一个天桥
When the train derailed, it hit an overpass.
餐车的车顶转开飞了出去
The dining car roof sheared off and sliced through a passenger car.
然后切开了一个旅客的汽车.
There were multiple decapitations. Your guy can live without his leg.
造成了大量的伤亡.
你那家伙没有腿也能活.
这绝对不仅仅是关于那条腿或那个人.
This is so not about the leg. Or the guy.
但是谢谢
But thank you. For all that you do. Really. Thanks.
为所有你做的那些而感谢,真的
Mm-hmm,yeah. Oh,yeah,亲爱的,我们没事
Yeah, honey, we're fine.
Yeah,但是一些农民开着汽车超火车
Some redneck tried to outrun the train, then they give us this boy doctor.
然后他们就走了, 留给我们这个乳臭未干的小医生
All right, scar shouldn't be too bad.
好了,疤痕不会太明显
能告诉我,我朋友怎么了吗?
Can you tell me... My friend... She's pregnant too.
她也怀孕了
She went in a different ambulance. She was burned. Do you know where she is?
她被送进另外一个救护车了
她有烧伤
你知道她在哪里吗
If she's not here, she should be in Maternity.
如果她不在这左右的话 她应该在妇产科那边.
Okay,我要去看她
I need to see her.
我们这里还没完呢,你还需要做一个全面的检查
- We're not finished here. - My baby's fine. I feel her kicking.
我孩子没事
- I've got to see Brooke. - You can't just leave.
我能感觉到她在踢我,我要去看brooke.
uh,等等,你不能就这样走了
[Alex] Just wait. Come here, come here.
等等.过这边来
Ow! Ow!
Ow. Ow!
-Sorry. -你之前刚刚做了个心脏手术,george.
Sorry.
So you operated on a heart earlier. You'd think you could draw blood.
你要想想你抽点血根本没问题.
我玩那心脏玩好久呢.
- I rocked that heart. - Yeah, you did.
是啊,的确.
I think I'm strung out on the scalpel.
我觉得我对解剖刀上瘾了,
没什么不好的
Nothing wrong with that.
那个,有什么消息吗?.关于...
So any news? About...
没有. 我搞不清楚他.
No. I can't read him.
我觉得这有点令人惊讶
I think it's pretty amazing you even gave him the choice.
你甚至连选择都给他了
And I think, for what it's worth,
我觉得为了值得的事情
如果他没选你的话,他可是疯到家了.
I think he's crazy if he doesn't pick you.
拜托告诉我你们见到了一只右腿
Please tell me you've seen a right leg, a cleanly severed right leg.
一只干净整洁的右腿.
No.
没看到.
这工作到底多变态?
How weird is this job?
变态.
Weird.
Brooke?
- Brooke? - Jana?
Jana?
谢天谢地.
- Thank God. - Dr. Karev?
-Karev医生? 她也在火车上? -我阻止不了她,她要过来看她
- I couldn't stop her. - She was on the train?
-是的 -你做了超声波吗?
- Yes, but... - Have you done an ultrasound?
清除了她的C脊骨?
Cleared her C-spine?
有什么原因你可以认为这个病人
Is there a reason why she is wandering around the hospital unattended?
可以随意在医院里到处漫游而无人照料?
She's not unattended. I came up with her. She's...
她不是没人照料的,我和她一起来的
你现在可以走了,
You can leave now, Dr. Karev.
Karev医生.
太不负责任了, 即使对一个实习生来说.
Irresponsible even for an intern.
怎么,你不同意?
What? You disagree?
她要来看她的朋友.
She wanted to see her friend. I mean, what was he supposed to do, tackle her?
我是说,他能怎么办? 把她捆起来?
Stevens医生,为什么你不去 把我们的新患者送上床呢?
Dr. Stevens, why don't you get our new patient into a bed? Shall we?
可以吗?
能感觉到这个吗, krasnoff小姐?
Can you feel that, Miss Krasnoff?
你是个帅医生.
You're a cute doctor. Cute doctors get to call me by my first name.
帅医生应该直接叫我名字
Bonnie.
- Bonnie? - Mmm.
Okay,bonnie.
OK, Bonnie. Can you feel that, Bonnie?
能感觉到这个吗bonnie?
Can I feel what? Oh. Well, I guess that's a no.
我能感觉到什么?
Oh. Oh,那我猜是感觉不到了.
-对不起 -shepherd医生? -嗯?
- [George] Dr. Shepherd? - Yes.
我拿到检查结果了.
- I got the labs. - Great, thank you.
oh,太好了,谢谢
Here you go. Hold that, please.
拿着这个.
Could you try to wiggle your toes, Mr. Maynard?
你能试着动动你的脚趾吗 Maynard先生?
动了吗?
- Are they moving? - Yes, they are.
是的,动了.
- Good. That's good, right? - Yes, it is. Yes, it is.
好,好现象对吗?
是的,那是.
What about me? Are mine moving?
我呢?我的动了吗?
是的,也动了
Yes, they are.
Yay 我
Yay me.
Shepherd医生,对吗? 嗯,对
- [Man] Dr. Shepherd, is it? - Yes, it is.
Shepherd医生,
Dr. Shepherd, Bonnie and I...
bonnie 和我..
我们要一直这样生活吗?
- are we going to live through this? - Now that's just morose, Tom.
这问题可有点郁闷了,tom.
I'm sorry, dear.
对不起,亲爱的.
医生?
Doctor?
我们会尽全力做所有我们能做的,Maynard先生.
We're going to do everything we can, Mr. Maynard.
时间啊,yang.
About time. I was starting to think my work here would be wasted.
我都开始考虑,我在这里工作简直是一种浪费
真对不起,不太好找啊
So sorry. It wasn't easy to find.
我检查了伤口
I checked the wound and it's very clean cut, well preserved.
切面很好,而且保存的不错
Dr. Webber?
Webber医生?
先生?
Sir?
注意到那关于那腿的其他事情了吗?
Notice anything else about that leg? Anything other than that very clean cut?
除了非常整洁的切面之外的任何其他事情?
你是否真的注意到其他,例如
Did you happen to notice, for example, that it was shaved recently?
最近是不是刮腿毛了
And manicured? Take a look at my patient, Dr. Yang.
修过指甲吗?
仔细看看我的病人,yang医生
他是那种看起来像是
Does he look like a man who woke up and shaved one of his legs this morning?
今早只刮一只腿的腿毛的男人吗?
不像.
No.
我马上去找,那个um,对的
I'll go find the right... the right right leg.
那个对的右腿...对的右腿...
- The right... - Thank you.
谢谢
有什么进展了
- Where are we? - You were right. Vitals are erratic.
Pulse is weak. The spine's severed. I was hoping that it didn't hit.
But from that angle, it just can't have missed the aorta.
那男人如何了?觉得他能活下来?
What about him? Think he can live?
他有更大的机会
- He's got better odds. - Let OR One know we're coming.
那好吧,去通知手术室我们马上过来
o'malley?
And, O'Malley, close off the gallery. We don't need an audience for this.
把展示窗关上
我们不需要任何观众围观
她还在开玩笑呢
She's cracking jokes.
你如何告诉某人她马上就要死了,
How do you tell someone she'll be dead soon when she's cracking jokes?
还在她坐在那里开玩笑的时候
请问.
Excuse me? Is there any chance that we can get out of here some time this year?
有什么机会我们能离开这里吗
-今年某些时候? -那个,测试结果还没出来
Well, the lab's backed up and so is Radiology.
X光结果也没出来.
I can't discharge her until I know she has no internal injuries.
在我没确定她没有任何内伤之前 我不能让你朋友出院.
[Cell phone rings]
Hello? Yeah,我们还在这里呢
[Yvonne] Hello? Yeah, we're still here,
因为我们的医生真tmd没用.
'cause the doctor's friggin' useless. Mm-hm.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
I realize you're dealing with a lot of carnage.
我了解你正在处理大量的伤亡患者.
我只想问问,如果你可能从那伤亡人口中
I'm asking if you could maybe sift through some of that carnage
筛下什么来,或者找到...
and find a... Hello... Dammit.
hello?该死.
Cristina. You paged me?
Cristina,你呼我了?
If I don't find this leg, the chief is gonna cut me from this program.
如果我找不到那只腿
头就会把我从这个手术中赶出来
And I cannot go back home, Burke. It is too sunny in Los Angeles.
我不能回家去burke.
L.A实在是太阳光普照了. 而且是每天都那么阳光明媚
It's sunny every day.
那么你呼我是因为?
And you paged me because?
我需要你帮我找到那条腿
I need you to help me find the leg.
我检查了公告版,你没有手术对吧?
I checked the board. You're not in surgery, right?
你是我男朋友!我是说...
You're my boyfriend. I mean...
我知道,对这种事情我没什么经验
I know I don't have much experience with this kind of thing,
但是...
but aren't boyfriends supposed to help in situations like this?
男朋友不是用来救场的吗
尤其是在这种情况下?
Cristina, when we're on duty, I can't be your boyfriend.
Cristina,当我们在值班的时候,我不能做你男朋友
Okay?
OK, so when we're on duty, I can have sex with someone else?
Okay,所以,当我们在值班的时候,
我能和其他什么人做爱?
Yang医生,我可走了啊
Dr. Yang, I'm walking away now.
好,很好.
Fine. Fine. But when the chief cuts me, you might rethink this.
但是当头儿一旦把我赶出来, 你就会重新考虑这个了
Addison在病人面前大声训斥你?
Addison yelled at you in front of a patient?
她倒没有特别大声.
She didn't exactly yell.
好吧,她是魔鬼的妓女.
- Fine, she's Satan's whore. - Thank you. So did you yell back?
谢谢,那你跟她喊回去了吗?
没有
- No. - Dude, you lost your mojo.
-伙计,你真失去你的本性了 -再说一次?
- Excuse you? - I was trying to talk boy.
我只是试图和你聊天,小子.
O'Malley plugs a hole with his finger and he's a hero.
O'malley 只不过把手指塞在个洞里罢了
周围的人全都把他当成什么了不起的大英雄了.
- I have one off day... - You chickened out.
-我有权利休息一天.. -你胆小如鼠
-我只不过犹豫了一小会儿而已 -为什么你不吻izzie?
I hesitated briefly.
Why didn't you kiss lzzie?
嗯..我要走了
- And now I'm leaving. - It's not in the morgue.
也不在太平间
I've looked in the ambulances, in the ER...
我找过救护车了,找过急诊室
为啥一个tmd的流血的毛腿 就这么毁了我的职业生涯了?
How is one bloody, hairy leg going to destroy my career?
Karev医生?
[Man] Dr. Karev?
我希望你找回原来个性的自己alex.
I hope you find your mojo, Alex. I find you disturbing without it.
-我发现没有那个性,你有点心烦意乱 -我也希望.
[Alex] Me too.
Ow.
- [Thud] - Ow!
这个有点难度,因为你们的身体
[Derek] This is hard, because your body is in a certain amount of shock.
正处在一定数量级的振荡当中.
可以防止你们感觉到疼痛
It's preventing you from feeling pain, feeling the extent of your injuries.
也可以防止
你们伤口的扩大.
Shepherd医生?
[Bonnie] Dr. Shepherd.
这金属竿子在我们体内
We have a metal pole cutting a path through our insides.
开出一条小路来穿过我们.
我不知道tom如何想的
I don't know about Tom here,
但是我没期待
but I didn't expect to walk out of here anytime soon, so...
什么时候能从这里走出去...
无论是什么方法,决定 你需要告诉我们的
whatever it is you have to say, just please, say it.
请你尽管说.
Okay,bonnie.
[Derek] OK, Bonnie.
为了给Maynard先生做手术,
In order to operate on Mr. Maynard, we have to separate you two.
我们必须把你们俩先分开.
为了手术而分开
In order to do that, we have to move you backwards off the pole.
我们需要把你向后移动,直到移下竿子.
你不能同时把竿子从我俩中拉下来吗?
Can't you just pull the pole out of both of us?
如果我们这样做
If we did that, you would both start bleeding very quickly. Too quickly.
你们俩都会大量出血,非常迅速
此时那竿子正塞住伤口.
Right now the pole is plugging the wounds.
一旦移动
Once removed, the organs will shift.
所有脏器全部跟着移动
And there is a great deal of damage.
同时会造成大量的毁坏
那么如果你们移动我的话...
So, if you move me, I'll die?
我就会死?
我们会做一切我们能做的...
We're gonna do everything we can to...
no. No.
[Tom] No. No. If anybody has to go, it should be me.
如果有人需要死的话
- You just move me... - No, Mr. Maynard.
那应该是我. 你们就移动...
Maynard先生,Maynard先生,
Mr. Maynard.
你的伤害扩张的可能比较小
Your injuries are less extensive.
如果我们把竿子从你这边拿出来 并在那四周手术的话
If we pull the pole from you as we operate around it,
我们有更大的机会来救治创伤.
we have a better chance of repairing the damage.
这不对
It's not right.
这不公平.
It's not fair.
Tom...
Tom.
任何一种方法都不公平
It's not fair either way.
那个,um...
Is um... Is my Danny... Is he here yet?
我家danny...他来了吗?
班机延迟了.
There are delays at the airport. The storm...
Um,因为暴风雪...
We could wait.
我们可以等, 但是我们等的越久
But the longer we do, the higher the risk of infection for...
感染的危险性就越高...
不,不用等.
No. No.
这个更好一些
This is better.
Danny 不会理解的
Danny, he wouldn't understand.
我已经有几个小时来处理所有这些
I've had a couple of hours to, you know, process all of this,
但是如果他看到我了, 和我说一些话,我...
but if... if he had to see me, talk to me like this...
well,我只是觉得那将会非常难过
Well, I just think it would be too hard.
[Both inhale and exhale]
就在那里... 在脊椎间隔里.
[Addison] Right there. In between the vertebral spaces.
不要害怕加压.
Don't be shy about pressure.
很好,你做的很好
That's good. You are doing so good.
有人叫公证人了吗?
- Somebody called for a notary? - I asked for a lawyer.
我是想找个律师
I couldn't get one at this time of night.
在这夜深人静的时候我可找不到.
But the hospital has pretty standard forms.
但是医院有多种多样的标准表格.
比如如果意外死亡
It says that in the case of death or permanent vegetative state,
或者变成植物人,
your child remains in the custody of... We put her name in.
那样的话,你的子女将会在某人的监护下
我们会把她的名字放上去
Wait. What? What are we... Who's dying here?
等等,什么? 我们是什么? 这里谁要死了?
有些危险. 任何手术都有危险
There's some danger. With any surgery, there's danger.
就brooke的烧伤来说
But with the trauma of Brooke's burns, there's an additional risk of shock.
有休克的额外风险.
- She wants to be certain. - That's ridiculous.
-她只是想有个保障而已. -这可真荒谬,你太荒谬了.
You're going to be fine, do you hear me?
-你马上就没事了,你听到我的话了吗? -我听到了.
I hear you. But we still have to sign the forms
但是我们还是需要签字
除非你想把我们的儿子最后交给我妈.
unless you want our son to end up with my mom.
你们俩在一起多久了?
How long have you two been together?
从3年级开始.
Since third grade.
我们不是爱人,只是最好的朋友而已
We're not lovers, we're best friends. We wanted our kids to have two parents.
我们只是希望我们的孩子有两个父母.
- So we got a sperm donor... - The same donor?
所以我们找了个精子捐赠人
同一个捐赠人?那么你们的孩子是兄妹了?
So your babies are brother and sister?
Oh,太牛X了啊
How cool is that?
-真是... -wow.
- That's... Wow. - [Trickling]
-湿了. -什么?
- Wet. - What?
我湿了
I'm wet. I think my water just broke.
-Oh,天. -我猜我的羊水刚刚破了.
好消息
Good news. You've got a broken rib, we're gonna give you some painkillers.
你的一根肋骨坏了.
我们会给你一些止痛药...
-之后,你就应该可以出院了 -谢谢.
- After that you should be good to go. - Thank you.
[Cell phone rings]
Yvonne,接电话.
Yvonne, answer your phone.
Yvonne? Yvonne?
Yvonne?!
Yvonne!
蓝色警报, 我这里需要帮忙
- Code blue! I need some help here! - [Mary] Yvonne!
Yvonne?!
一个epi.拿住 c.p.r.
Push one of epi. Hold CPR.
她的腹部正在扩张,有固体在里面
Her abdomen is rock solid. She's lost too much blood.
她失了很多血,她必然是流血流了几个钟头.
- She's been bleeding for hours. - There's no blood.
但是根本没有血啊,她没流血.
- She was bleeding internally. - She didn't say anything.
她是内出血
她什么都没说 她没有...
- [continuous beep] - She was... She wasn't even a patient.
她甚至都不是个病人.
I didn't know.
我不知道
Karev医生,她死了
[Nurse] Dr. Karev, she's gone.
不不不!!!
[Mary] No! No!
不不不!!! Yvonne!
No! No! Yvonne!
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
死亡时间... 2:51.
Time of death, 2:51.
No! No! No!
[Mary] No, no, no, no.
Don't. Try again. Try again.
再试试,再试!
Jana,这是我们妇产科主治医生Hoffman医生.
Jana, this is our OB resident, Dr. Hoffman.
她从现在开始接管你.
She's gonna be taking care of you from here.
Uh-huh.
你做的非常好jana. 继续呼吸.
You're doing great, Jana, keep breathing.
我现在要检查一下你的宫颈.
I'm gonna check your cervix now.
Brooke, 我们预约了一个手术室
We've booked an OR but they won't hold it for long
但是他们不会保留太久,所以我们现在就要过去了.
- so we need to go now. - Right now?
现在?
But we're supposed to be together. We took classes.
但是我们应该是在一起的啊,我们一起上的产前培训课.
我很抱歉,我们等不了了.
- I'm sorry, but we can't wait. - That's OK, Brookie.
这没什么,brookie.你先去做你的剖腹产手术
You go have your C-section. And enjoy those drugs.
好好享用那麻醉药品咯
- This is already not fun for my vagina. - Dr. Stevens?
这对我的阴道来说可一点都不好玩
Stevens医生.
- No. If I have to go, she has to stay. - Someone has to stay with Jana. Please.
No.
如果我必须去的话,她必须留下来
至少留个人来照顾jana吧,拜托了?
Brooke, Dr. Stevens is a surgeon, but I'm gonna...
Brooke,Stevens医生是个外科医生
-但是我会帮你找一个... -我可以.
It's OK. I'll stay.
我留下来.
Okay.
OK.
Brookie,
Brookie. Stay alive, OK?
坚强一点,好吗??
你也是.
You too.
真该死!
Dammit!
Hey,医生?
- [Man] Hey, Doc. - What?!
干吗?!
Easy, killer. Jill said you guys were freaking out looking for this leg.
放松点
Jill说你们找这条破腿都找疯了啊
-谢谢 -不用谢
- Thank you. - No problem.
好极了
[Alex] Right on.
webber主管,我非常非常抱歉,我...
Chief Webber, I'm extremely sorry, I...
把这个腱和这些提取物一起拉下来.
[Richard] Pull that tendon down with those pick-ups.
Oh,你找到那腿了?
- You found the leg? - I found the leg.
我找到了这腿.
[Richard] You missed out on this, but I'm sure they could use a hand in ER.
你错过这场好戏了,yang.
但是我肯定急诊室那边肯定需要人手帮忙
Karev和我从现在开始完全可以处理这个了.
Karev and I can handle it from here.
[Richard] Suction.
能问你个问题吗?
- Can I ask you a question? - Mm-hm.
Mm-hmm.
你信有天堂吗
Do you believe in heaven?
我信.
I do.
你不信吗?
Don't you?
我想要相信.
I want to.
Bonnie...
[Tom] Bonnie...
我只是想说...
[Tom] I just want to say...
shh.
Shhh!
我知道
I know. I know.
我知道.
这位是Adams医生...
[Derek] This is Dr. Adams, our anesthesiologist.
我们的麻醉师.
When you're ready, he's going to put you to sleep.
当你们做好准备的时候
他将会让你们睡去
那么就不会疼了?
So it's not gonna hurt?
一点也不会疼
[Adams] It won't hurt a bit.
真好,Yeah.
Good.
这可真好
That's good.
Shepherd医生?
- Dr. Shepherd? - Yes?
Yes.
You're gonna be the one to talk to my Danny, right?
你会是那个告诉我家danny的人对吗?
Yes.
Okay.
- OK. - OK.
你想要我告诉他什么?
What would you like me to tell him?
为什么我感觉好像我们要杀了这姑娘似的?
[Bailey] Why do I feel like we're about to kill this girl?
Bailey医生?
Dr. Bailey, my labs are in.
-我血测试出来了. -镇定下来了?
- Sober? - Can I scrub in?
我能加入了吗?
Do it fast.
快点吧.
George.
- George. - Right.
Hey.
Hi.
你知道吗,我去过酒吧了?
- You know, I went to the bar. - I heard.
我听说了
你注射的时候加了阿司匹林吗?
You take some aspirin with the banana bag? Helps with the hangover.
可以帮助你减轻宿醉.
Oh.
[Meredith] Oh.
你和她在一起了
You're staying with her.
Yeah,她是我老婆.
Yeah, she's my wife.
Shepherd医生,她就要不行了.
- [Bailey] Dr. Shepherd, she's crashing. - [beeping]
发生什么事了?
[Derek] What happened?
我刚把他们麻醉了,这竿子动了.
- [Adams] I just put them under. - The pole must've shifted.
-我几乎没碰到她.这不是我的过错 -这不是任何人的错
I barely touched her. This isn't my fault.
It's nobody's fault. We need to remove her now.
如果想要任何机会的话,我们需要再移动她.
- How do we do this? - [Burke] Team One, stabilize his body.
-怎么做? -第一小组继续保持他身体的稳定
第二小组把她向后移,然后用锯.
Team Two, move her back and let's get the saw in there.
大家注意,一定要迅速而且流畅
This has to be fast and smooth, people.
O'malley,适当的抓住这竿子.
O'Malley, you hold the pole in place.
不管你做什么,千万别用力拉.
- Whatever you do, don't let it move. - OK.
-不要让它移动 -Okay.
[Burke] On the count of three. One, two...
大家准备.
1... 2...
3! 很好
Three!
That's great. That's great. Take another breath. One, two...
做的很好,再呼吸一次.
1... 2...
[Addison] He's wedged under her ribs, we have to pull him out.
这孩子楔入她的肋骨下了了.
我们需要把他拔出来,大家准备.
On three. One, two...
1... 2...
- [nurse] Watch her head. - [Nurse] Clean towel.
[Saw whirs]
- [Burke] He's stable. - [Derek] Retract.
他现在稳定下来了, 让我们看看她那边的情况怎么样了.
[Burke] Let's start with her and see what we can do.
- [Bailey] We'll need more blood. - Scalpel.
手术刀
Uh,grey?过这边来
- [Burke] Hold onto the blood bag. - [Bailey] Grey, help retract.
过来帮忙缩进.
[Derek] Richardson retractor.
医生.
- [Burke] Lap. - [Bailey] Got it.
牵引器.
[Derek] Clamp.
[Burke] Retractor.
[Derek] Quick, please. Give me some sponges. Sponges.
- Bovie suction here. - I'm in.
我进来了
[Derek] Lap sponges. Hand me the cautery.
她的大动脉已经撕碎了.
Her aorta's shredded. She's gonna bleed out.
-这里太多损坏了 -她没有心跳了.
We have no rhythm.
医生,他血压正在急剧下降
[Adams] Doctors, he's losing pressure.
他在流血.
- [Burke] He's bleeding. - [Derek] Let's go.
[Man] Transitioning.
[Man] Change out. Everybody change gloves.
她怎么办?我们不能就这样遗弃她了啊?
[Meredith] What about her? We can't just abandon her!
来人啊
- [Burke] I'm going in. - [Meredith] We can't abandon her!
我们不能就这样遗弃她了
[Burke] I'm going in stem to stern. Scalpel.
我要从支架开始做.手术刀.
胸骨锯.
[Bailey] Sternal saw.
[Burke] Give me the sternal saw.
[Derek] Cautery.
- [Bailey] Let's go. - [Derek] Meredith.
Meredith.
[Bailey] Dr. Grey.
Grey医生?
- [George] Meredith! - What about her?
Meredith?
We cannot just abandon her. We have an obligation.
她怎么办?我们不能就这样遗弃她
我们有职责!
[Bailey] I'll take care of this.
Meredith,算了,她的损伤实在太大了.
Meredith, come on, there was too much damage.
再没有任何事情我们可以做的了
There was never anything we could do. We have to let her go.
我们必须让她走了
死亡时间...
[Bailey] Time of death 3:49.
3:49.
早上好.
- Good morning. - How's Brooke?
brooke好吗?
She's good.
-她挺好的 -孩子呢?
- And the baby? - He came through, too.
他也挺过来了
你决定好了吗 Stevens医生?
So, have you made a decision yet, Dr. Stevens?
你说什么?
I'm sorry?
是否决定要讨厌我,还是不.
Whether or not you're going to hate me.
你是meredith的朋友,我是邪恶的老巫婆
You're Meredith's friend. I'm the wicked witch who cheated on Dr...
毁了她的生活,还背着医生搞外遇...
等一下,你们是怎么叫他来着?
Wait, what is it that you guys call him?
"美梦先生"
McDreamy.
没错.
Right. God, doesn't that embarrass him?
天,这个没让他觉得尴尬吗?
是啊,我想他觉得了.
Yeah, I think it does.
Yeah,所以,不管怎么说,你都应该讨厌我.
- By all rights, you should hate me. - I guess.
我猜是吧.
Except that I'm gonna be staying in town for a while.
除非我决定在这里呆一段时间.
-是吗? -嗯.
- You are? - Yes.
我觉得你在我妇科领域还挺有天赋的
And you show a real gift with my specialty.
如果你想学的话,我有大把东西可以教你
And I have a lot to teach, if you want to learn.
所以?
So...
所以如果你决定了
So, when you decide how important it is for you to hate me, let me know.
你讨厌我到底有多重要的时候,告诉我.
[Woman on PA]
她,uh...
Did she uh... Did she suffer?
她走的很痛苦吗?
不,她的伤害正好阻止了...
No. Her injuries prevented her from...
没有,她一点痛苦都没有
No, she wasn't in any pain.
很好.
Good. That's...
这个...
她让我...
She asked me to... to tell you that...
告诉你...
她想让你知道,
She wanted you to know that if love were enough...
如果爱的力量足够伟大的话...
如果爱的力量足够伟大的话,
that if love were enough, that she'd still be here with you.
她还是会一直陪在你身边的
做为医生...
[Meredith] As surgeons,
太多的事情我们需要了解了.
there are so many things we have to know.
做的不错 Karev医生.
- Fine work, Dr. Karev. - Thank you, sir.
谢谢,先生.
We have to know we have what it takes.
我们要了解我们需要掌握的.
我们要了解如何照顾病人
We have to know how to take care of our patients.
Tom现在情况非常好.
[Burke] Tom is doing just fine.
[& Emiliana Torrini: Today Has Been Okay]
[Chime]
还有如何彼此照顾
And how to take care of each other.
[Bell rings]
[Derek sniffles]
Okay?
- OK? - Yeah.
Yeah.
[Ringing stops]
最终..
Eventually we even have to figure out...
我们更要了解
如何照顾我们自己.
how to take care of ourselves.
作为医生,
As surgeons, we have to be in the know.
我们必须一直了解
但是作为人类,
But as human beings,
有时候处在黑暗中其实更好一些
sometimes it's better to stay in the dark.
因为...
Because in the dark, there may be fear...
黑暗中也许会有恐惧...
但同时也有希望.
but there's also hope.
你们最好去洗个澡把自己弄干净.
Better get cleaned up. Rounds. Five minutes.
自由活动5分钟.
-=风软FRM字幕组=- 翻译:Parry Wong (澳洲) 校对:Parry Wong (澳洲)
Grey's Anatomy 206 风软论坛 荣誉出品 www.1000fr.com